6. Abusuzu
7. Zenitsu
8. J.D concert
12. warrior
11. defeat
13. king of the night
10. shimmendo
a
We are TOKIMEKI ADVERTISEMENT!
Did you notice?
Look at this!
We look like models!
Today, we are shooting a collaboration
video with Tokimeki Advertisement and
Spince!
It's so fun!
We are going to be models for fashion
this time, so we are wearing the same
clothes.
We are wearing girly clothes.
Look! We changed the color!
It's a coincidence.
The stylist chose the color for us.
It's so fresh!
We don't usually do this.
I love wearing casual clothes.
It's like a shop.
It's so fresh!
Look at the back.
It's fashionable!
It's a fashionable look.
We are wearing a scarf like a princess.
It's like a princess.
It's cute.
I'm so happy.
I'm wearing an outerwear and she is
wearing a scarf.
It's so fun.
We are going to be like Bambi in
autumn.
Yeah!
We are going to enjoy it!
Wow, it's so stylish!
Cute!
We took a photo on the fashion page for
the first time.
We are a tweed style.
We are a girly style.
We are not cute.
We all have similar clothes.
I like this style.
I was very happy.
We were searched maturely.
Bambi doesn't look like a middle school
student.
We were searched maturely.
Middle school students are very
popular.
We were searched maturely.
I was searched maturely.
Please speak softly.
Please use this scene.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I'm wearing brown color LATTE.
I wore this color outerwear.
I matched with this LATTE color.
I wore this for the first time. It's so
cute.
This is easy to match with a turtleneck
skirt.
It's easy to wear even one.
Please check it out.
The back side is also cute.
It's cute.
I'll wear this outerwear.
I feel gorgeous just by wearing this.
It's warm because it's winter.
It's warm.
It's cute.
It's comfortable to touch.
It's comfortable.
Please touch it.
And this.
I thought it was cute.
I want you to see this.
There is a bear.
I'm in love with a bear.
I'm wearing a hair style and hair
arrangement in a modern way.
It's a new style.
I always wear a hair tie.
I thought it would be good to try this
style.
I'm wearing a nice outfit.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I like this headband.
I like this pants.
I wanted to wear this kind of clothes.
I'm so happy.
Everyone has roses.
Really?
It's true.
Yeah!
Let's go to the rose field!
I'm going to take a picture of roses.
Please subscribe to this channel.
It was fun.
We are like street fashion.
We are cool.
We have never worn this color.
This is the first time to wear this
color.
We are cool.
Please subscribe to our channel.
It's a new style.
We can't wear this kind of clothes
normally.
I haven't worn this kind of clothes for
shooting.
It was a new challenge and I enjoyed
it.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I have glasses.
I don't usually wear transparent
glasses, so it was very new.
It was fun.
We want to do it again.
The last is constante
It's cute!
Isn't this necklace cute?
I like this jacket.
It's cute.
I can wear this alone.
It's amazing.
It's cute.
It's warm.
It's light.
It's simple and cute.
I recommend this to everyone.
I'm so happy that I can collaborate
with Toki-sen and make products again.
I'm glad that I can make products with
three different styles of clothes.
I'm sure you'll see us in a different
way.
This jacket is a street style and looks
cool.
I think it'll be stylish and cool if I
wear this one.
It's warm and I like it.
It's one size, so it's a little big for
me.
But, it's stylish if I wear it a
little.
It's a monotone color, so it's easy to
match with anything.
You may think it's cool.
But, if I take it off, the sweater
inside will be...
It's a collaboration product.
It's brown and casual.
Can you see the back?
It's casual with a lock on the back.
I can wear it in a cool way.
It's brown, so I think it'll be cute to
wear it with a brown skirt or pants.
And, this one.
It's Toki-sen's color.
And this one.
It's the same key ring.
It's Tokimeki-sen's.
I like it.
I got them one by one and I'll put them
on my school bag.
It's colorful and poppy, so I think
it'll be cute.
It's cute to wear it with a simple bag.
It's made of silicon, so it's not
fragile.
I have three collaboration products, so
please try them on and enjoy them!
That's all for today. Thank you for
watching!
Thank you very much!
We've finished our collaboration with
Petose Pins!
We're wearing a set, jacket and key
chain.
They're all so cute and easy to wear.
They're warm and soft.
They're cute.
We also divided the sets into 3
categories.
We had a lot of fun shooting in 3
Please try to get these items.
They're all stylish.
You can wear them in various ways.
Please enjoy wearing them in your
favorite way.
Please try to wear them in our way.
Please check them out.
See you!
I'm sure I'll be satisfied.
I'll surpass.
I'll record it forever.
I'll make you satisfied.
This is the last show to show the final
performance.
So, I think the excitement is the most
important thing in this year.
This is a big and important show for
us.
We can't finish this year without this
show.
I think this is a show that we can
connect with everyone and share our
feelings.
We have been working hard for this year
to make this show a success.
So, I want to say to everyone that this
is a very important show for us.
I want to have a good show every year.
I want to make a good show with
everyone.
I want to show the old Toki-san of
Iwamura.
I think that Toki-san is the brightest
at that time.
I want everyone to see the show that we
are going to do.
If you want to come, please come to the
show.
We will definitely make a legendary
If you want to come, please come.
We will show you the show that you
can't miss now.
I want everyone to come to the Toki-
san's live show with a smile.
E까지
Aqua Area!
It's sparkling!
It's shining!
Please subscribe to my channel!